

SUMMARY

I'm a UX/UI Designer with a background in retail and fashion.

I'm passionate about Visual Design and User Experience because it represents the perfect balance between creative and analytical thinking. I like the idea that what I do connects businesses and individuals through problem solving and design.

	+44 (0)7475 129704
\bowtie	rick@rickveronese.com
	rickveronese.com
in	/rickveronese

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE WEB DESIGNER

Self Employed | Apr 2013 - Present

- Website design for various types of clients ranging from entrepreneurs to small-sized businesses.
- Market and User research
- Wordpress training for clients

UX/UI DESIGNER

Designlab | Oct 2016 - Apr 2017

- Responsive websites and mobile app design for different industries: eCommerce and Music entertainment
- UX Research (Competitive Analysis, User Interviews, User Surveys and Data Analytics)
- Site and apps architectures (User Flows, Sitemaps, Wireframes, Prototypes)
- Branding and UI kits

EDUCATION

UX/UI DESIGN

Designlab | 2016-2017

An intensive UX/UI design course with real life projects and more than $480\ logged$ hours.

MARKETING & SALES

Doube Your Freelancing Academy |

Marketing and Business based course on creating a freelancing business and self-promotion.

WEB DESIGN

Mlwebco | 2013/2014

This online course helped me kickstart my freelance web design career with basic Adobe Fireworks and HTML/CSS

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Born in Italy, I've lived in the UK for the past 3 years and I like learning new languages. The next goal is taking Spanish up to 100% and learn a new language.





SPANISH 40%



REFERENCES

Luca Longo | Head of UX Design

Hotelbeds Group

mail: lux.longo@gmail.com

Sara Vilas Santiago | Senior UX Designlab

mail: saravssantiago@gmail.com

SKILLS

User Experience

Interaction Design

Prototyping
Wireframes
Usability
Testing

Research

TOOLS & SOFTWARE

Sketch

Photoshop Illustrator

Invision/Marvel

HTML/CSS

